savorthesuccess.com 2018-12-19

# Savor the Success Privacy Policy - Savor the Success - Business Network for women entrepreneurs

Effective Date: May 25, 2018  
Savor the Success, LLC (hereinafter referred to as "STS") respects and values your privacy.  

This Privacy Policy details how STS treats the information that is gathered about you when you join the STS website, www.savorthesuccess.com (hereinafter referred to as the "Site"), post a profile on the Site or use the services offered by STS on the Site.  By registering for an account or using the services on the Site, you expressly consent to the collection, use, disclosure and storage of such information as set forth in this Privacy Policy and in STS's Terms and Conditions.

 **Collection of Information:**

Non Personally Identifiable Information (Cookies):  
STS uses cookies solely for internal recordkeeping and aggregating data about the traffic on the Site.  Third parties may, however, be placing and reading cookies on your users' browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being shown on your screen.  If you choose not to accept cookies from the Site or from third parties, you may disable that option through your web browser.    

When someone visits our websites, we automatically receive their computer’s IP address.

If you use any features available on our website by a third party, it may result in information being shared between us and the third party. For example, if you use Facebook’s “Like” feature, Facebook may register it and may post that information on Facebook, or ads from our company may appear in your stream.

**Cookies:**

We use “cookies,” including tracking pixels. These pixels are connected to outside platforms, which may include Google, Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Pinterest, Instagram, and other companies.

**Personally Identifiable Information:**

When you sign up for an account, STS requires that you provide certain personally identifiable information which may include:

\- first and last name,   
\- phone number,   
\- zip code,   
\- date of birth,   
\- email address, and   
\- any other personally identifiable information that you submit in correspondence with STS, in your STS profile or on the Site.

STS does not allow children under the age of 13 on the Site, nor does STS knowingly collect any information from any person under the age of 13.  If STS is informed that a profile or user account is being made by a person under the age of 13, STS will immediately remove the posting and any personally identifiable information that may have been inadvertently collected by STS.

Your safety is important to us.  Please keep in mind that any information you provide to anyone you meet through the Site is not covered by this Privacy Policy.  Remember to be vigilant about protecting your personal information.  If you are going to meet someone that you have connected with on the Site, STS recommends that you meet them in a public place.

 **Use of Personally Identifiable Information:**

STS will use the personally identifiable information that it collects about you to contact you in response to consumer-initiated inquiries, to provide the services to you that you request, to alert you to changes in services or features, and to provide you with requested information regarding STS or our services.  We may, from time to time, contact you about offers that we, or third parties with which we may partner, have that we believe, in our sole discretion, may interest you.

STS reserves the right to release current or past user information: (a) in the event that we believe that the Site is being or has been used in violation of STS's Terms and Conditions or to commit unlawful acts; (b) upon receipt of a properly authorized and authenticated governmental request for information; (c) in response to a subpoena or a court order, (d) to comply with relevant laws; (e) in response to an investigation of fraud regarding a specific consumer; (f) in an effort to safeguard the person or property of a STS employee or a third party; or (g) if STS is sold or acquired. 

Moreover, you hereby consent to disclosure of any record or communication to any third party when STS, in its sole discretion, determines the disclosure to be appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your e-mail address with other third parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time. 

If you no longer wish to receive emails from us which you have not specifically initiated, you may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the instructions contained in the applicable e-mail.  STS processes all unsubscribe requests in a prompt fashion.  
 **  
International Users:**

By using the Site and providing STS with data, you understand and agree that due to the international dimension of the Internet, STS may use the data collected in the course of our relationship as set forth in this Privacy Policy or in other communications with you, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. In addition, you acknowledge that your personally identifiable information and other data may be stored on servers located in the United States or in other international locations. By providing us with your information, you consent to the transfer and storage of such information. 

 **SPAM:**

STS does not tolerate Unsolicited Commercial Emails (also known as "SPAM") or other unsolicited emails to our users.  Your use of the services on the Site does not authorize you in any way to add other users of the Site to your physical or email mailing list without their express consent.  If it is brought to our attention that you are sending unsolicited emails to our users, we will immediately terminate your account and will cooperate with all legal authorities to aid in your prosecution for violations of state and federal SPAM laws.

 **Third Party Sites:**

Users listing products for sale or third party advertisers on the Site may direct you to a third party website.  Those websites are not affiliated with STS and their privacy policies may differ from STS's privacy policy.  STS is in no way responsible for the privacy policies or treatment of information from third party websites and strongly encourages you to review the privacy policies of every website you visit to determine what information they collect and how such information is handled by that website.

**How We Store Private Information:**

Our shopping cart and online payment processing is provided by Recurly and [Authorize.net](http://authorize.net/). Recurly retains our clients’ personal information, including credit card information. 

Our merchant processing company is Chase Paymentech. Chase retains personal information, and does not retain the credit card information.

**  
Storage of Information:**

_Profiles:  _  
All information submitted as part of your profile is stored until you request that your profile be removed.  We keep all information, even after a removal request is received, on our server for a minimum of ninety (90) days.  After that time, information may be purged from STS's servers periodically.  However, just because STS has purged the information from its servers does not mean that your information will not be archived by third party sources not affiliated with STS including, but not limited to, archive.org, google.com, and groups.yahoo.com.    
 _  
Personally Identifiable Information:    _   
Although STS does not release your personally identifiable information to the public and STS makes a reasonable good faith effort to store your personally identifiable information in a secure operating environment, we cannot guarantee 100% security of such information due to factors beyond our control.

 **Access or Questions:**

If you have any questions about our privacy policy or wish to review, or revise the personally identifiable information that STS has collected about you, you may send a written request to:

 _SAVOR THE SUCCESS, LLC  
114 Partition Street  
Saugerties, NY  12477_

STS may take reasonable steps to confirm your identity prior to supplying any personally identifiable information to you in order to prevent identity theft.  

 **Acceptance of and Changes to this Privacy Policy:**

By using the Site through any means, you hereby agree to this Privacy Policy in its entirety. STS reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to change, modify, add and/or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. 

All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Site. Please check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy constitutes your acceptance of any and all changes.

**Changes to Privacy Policy:**

We reserve the right to modify our privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently for updates. Changed and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on our website. If we make significant changes to our policy, current clients will be notified by email.
